Devesh Mhatre

FRONT-END WEB
DEVELOPER

Personal Info

Address

Behind Forest Office, Vadkhal, Pen Maharashtra, 402107

Phone

+91-9028250240

Email

deveshmhtr.mhatre92@gmail.com

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/devesh-mhatrea74192135

Website

devesh-mhatre.me

Skills

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript (ES6) & TypeScript

Sass

React & Gatsby

Linux

WordPress

Figma

Languages

English

Hindi

Marathi

ABOUT ME

From Python to C to Javascript, I have been tinkering with programming for half a decade now. But my initial attempts at web development were as appealing as any '90s website.

So, I started diving deeper into UI design as well. As a result, my websites started looking modern, and my confidence as a web developer started building.

Simultaneously, I also began paying attention to SEO best practices for web development. That was a great decision since it landed me a WFH gig that allowed me to build my web development skills without putting my life on hold.

EDUCATION

TILAK MAHARASHTRA VIDYAPEETH

2016 - 2019 | BACHELOR IN BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION

EXPERIENCE

01-2021 -PRESENT WAVEL AI

DIGITAL MARKETING INTERN

- Manage social media accounts using Hootsuite
- Manage company blog using WordPress
- Design and write content for social media marketing

10-2018 -01-2019 CUEMATH

- BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT INTERN
 - Corresponded with prospective customers and partners
 - Conducted live seminars and product demos
 - Helped automate daily report generation process

CERTIFICATIONS

12-2020 <u>freeCodeCamp - Responsive Web Design</u>

12-2020 <u>freeCodeCamp - JavaScript Algorithms and</u>

Data Structures

12-2020 <u>freeCodeCamp - Front End Libraries</u>

INTERESTS

Prolific reader, and not-so-prolific writer Hobbyist UI designer